arcadeaid.com 2017-12-11

# 42 Entertainment

42 ENTERTAINMENT PRIVACY POLICY

Introduction

42 Entertainment, LLC ("42 Entertainment") respects the privacy rights of our customers and is committed to protecting the information collected from you through our websites, social networking applications, software, and mobile applications ("Services"). To further this commitment, we have adopted a Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, use and disclose the information you provide to 42 Entertainment through our Services. 

This Privacy Policy describes:

  * The information we collect, how we do so and the purposes of our collection
  * How we use and with whom we share such information
  * How you can access and update such information
  * The choices you can make about how we collect, use and share your information
  * How we protect the information we store about you

By using our Services, you agree that your personal information will be handled as described in this Privacy Policy. Your agreement takes place when you "accept" or "allow" (or similar terms) one of our Services.

It is your responsibility to read and accept the terms of service and privacy policy for the Services and any third-party platform that allows access to our Services (e.g. social networking sites, mobile application stores). We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other entities, through which certain of our Services are offered or to which our Services may be connected. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by 42 Entertainment in connection with your use of our Services.

This Privacy Policy may be revised or updated at any time and we encourage you to check back often to ensure that you are familiar with the most recent version and the terms of our Privacy Policy.

1) Information We Collect

Technical and Usage Information

We receive and store certain types of non-personal technical information whenever you interact with us. For example, we automatically send and receive information to and from your computer which we use to automatically update (new features, bug fixes, etc.) our Services. We may collect your IP address, geolocation location information on mobile devices, operating system type, browser type, and other similar technical information. 

Like many other companies, we also use "cookies" and other automated tools to obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses our Services. While such information will typically be used in an aggregated way to improve our products and services, some information may be used to personalize your experience, or to offer you products and services specifically based on your preferences and usage.

Customer Support Correspondence

When you ask for assistance from our Customer Support team, we will collect and store the contact information you provide, information about your experience with our Services or activity on the Services.

Purchase Related Information

We receive and store the information you provide to 42 Entertainment when you make a purchase from 42 Entertainment or that you provide to us when you enter our transmedia experiences including certain promotions or sweepstakes. This personal information, such as first and last name, valid e-mail address and credit card billing data, may be necessary to purchase virtual currency, virtual items, enter a promotion or sweepstakes, or to otherwise transact business with us.

Information about You Received from a Social Networking Site, Your Application Store, or Mobile Device

If you access our Services using a mobile application from an app store or through a social networking site, certain information is available to us through those platforms. The information you allow 42 Entertainment to access varies by what experience of Service we are offering, but certain Services may be available via a social networking platform or mobile application store, and is affected by the privacy settings you establish on those sites. For example, 42 Entertainment may access and store some or all of the following information, as allowed by you, the social networking site, the application store, and your preferences on your mobile device including:

  * Your first and last name
  * Your profile picture or its URL on a social networking site
  * Your mobile device technical information if you access our Services through a mobile device
  * Your email address
  * Your physical location and that of your access devices through geolocation
  * Your gender
  * Your birthday
  * Your mobile device telephone number

SMS Notifications

We receive and store the information you provide, including your telephone number, when you sign up to have SMS notifications sent directly to your mobile phone. These messages notify you of activity on our Services and may allow you to play certain elements of our transmedia experiences from your phone. You can adjust the types of notifications you receive and when you receive them by editing your SMS notification settings. Standard text messaging rates apply. We will alert you if we ever use premium SMS texting.

2) How We Collect Information About You

Information about Users and Participation in Transmedia Experiences

When you participate in one of our transmedia experiences, 42 Entertainment collects and stores certain profile information that your provide directly or through our Services. We also collect information about your play interaction with other players and with us. The bulk of this information is collected and stored through the use of web logs, which are files on our web servers that record actions taken on our Services.

Communications Features

You may be able to take part in certain activities on our Services that give you the opportunity to communicate not only with 42 Entertainment, but with our users of our Services. These include:

  * Participating in player forums and message boards
  * Posting public comments to other users' profiles
  * Sending private messages or invitations to other users
  * Chatting with other users
  * Posting photos, video, or other content

We may record and store archives of these communications. You acknowledge and consent to the recording and storage of such communications.

Cookies

A "cookie" is a small file or record-keeping device that websites often store on a user's computer. Storage of cookies on your system provides an easy and convenient method for us to personalize your experience on our Services. For example, cookies will remember your username and password, tell us that you have played our Services before, and may contain other information that will make your next visit to our Services more enjoyable. You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer.

3) How We Use the Information We Collect

We may use the information we collect about you in any one or more of the following ways:

  * To register your account and allow you to participate in our experiences
  * To administer transmedia experiences and improve player interaction
  * To identify and suggest connections with other 42 Entertainment users
  * To enable user-to-user communications
  * To provide technical support and respond to user inquiries
  * To prevent fraud 
  * To notify users of in-fiction and other Service updates
  * To provide leader boards and promote player achievements
  * To communicate about new and current games
  * To solicit input and feedback to improve 42 Entertainment products and services and customize your user experience
  * To resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems
  * To analyze trends and user traffic and gather statistical information
  * To inform users about new products and promotional offers
  * To investigate and enforce terms of use violations

Additionally, 42 Entertainment and unaffiliated third parties may use the information we collect, such as your e-mail address, to respond to (i) customer support inquiries and (ii) keep you informed of your in-game activity, including comments from friends and notifications about in-game status. We may also send promotional e-mail messages directly or in partnership with parties other than 42 Entertainment. Of course, you may opt out of receiving such promotional messages at any time.

Importantly, many of our Services are on behalf of our clients that sponsor such Services. You information may be shared with those clients.

4) How We Share Information

Third Party Service Providers

42 Entertainment may employ and share your personal information with entities that use it to perform services on our behalf, such as payment processing, data analysis, e-mail delivery, hosting services, customer service and to assist us in our marketing efforts. We require all such entities to agree to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information and not to use your personal information for any other purpose. However, the information practices of other companies or people that 42 Entertainment does not employ or manage are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

Friends and Other 42 Entertainment Users

In some of our transmedia experiences other users will be able to see your account name and a profile. 

Jointly Offered Products and Services

From time to time we may offer products or services jointly with another entity, or may offer an additional product or service from another entity that in some way enhances or is related to a 42 Entertainment product or service. Examples include jointly developed, licensed or sponsored transmedia experiences, another entity's online service that is based on a 42 Entertainment game, or products or services that may enhance your gaming experience. In such cases, 42 Entertainment's use of your personal information is governed by this Privacy Policy, and the other entity's use of your personal information is governed by that entity's own privacy policy and/or terms of service.

Compliance with Law, Protecting our Property or Users, Sale and Merger

We may also disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, or that doing so is reasonably necessary to comply with legal processes, respond to any claims, or to protect the rights, property or personal safety of 42 Entertainment, our customers, or the public. In addition, information about our customers, including personal information, may be disclosed to a third party as part of any business transition, such as a bankruptcy, merger, sale, transfer of company assets, acquisition or similar event, if permitted by and done in accordance with applicable law. 

Third Party Advertisers

We do not actively share personal information with third party advertisers for their direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure. However, advertisers may obtain public information about you from your profile or other public sources.

We may use and share with third parties certain technical information (including IP addresses) or aggregated information to show general demographic and preference information among 42 Entertainment users. We may also allow advertisers to collect technical or aggregated information, which they may share with us, with tracking technologies like cookies and web beacons. (Beacons enable us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits the site on which the beacon is located, and to learn which banner ads bring users to a given site.)

5) Children's Privacy

We recognize the importance of safeguarding the privacy of children. To this end, 42 Entertainment does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from children under the age of 13. In the event we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe we have collected information on your child, please send an e-mail to info@42entertainment.com.

6) How to Access and Update Your Information

To manage the information 42 Entertainment receives about you from a mobile application store or social networking site you will need to follow the instructions at that site for updating your information and changing you privacy settings. 

If you no longer want 42 Entertainment to make active use of your information, or you wish to review or change the information 42 Entertainment has about you, you may send an e-mail to info@42entertainment.com. Requests will be processed as soon as possible. If you have any additional questions about this Privacy Policy, contact us at info@42entertainment.com.

7) Opting Out

You can always choose not to provide personal information to 42 Entertainment but doing so may prevent you from being able to play or take advantage of specific features of our Services.

If you no longer wish to receive promotional communications from us, you can opt out from receiving such communications from us at any time through those communications themselves. You may do so by e-mailing us at info@42entertainment.com. We will be happy to honor your request.

8) Security of Your Information

The security and confidentiality of your personal information is extremely important to us. We have implemented technical, administrative and physical security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access and improper use. To prevent unauthorized electronic access to personal information, we maintain information collected online behind a firewall-protected server; use SSL encryption for purchases made through our Services; and limit access only to those employees performing a legitimate business function. 

However, please understand that we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss or other breaches will never occur. Although we strive to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data while it is being transmitted to our site and any transmission is at your own risk. In addition, we urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe and to log out of your account after use. 

9) Customers Outside the United States

By using our Services, customers outside of the United States understand and agree that 42 Entertainment is a company based in the United States with servers based in the United States, and personal information will be transmitted into the United States and handled as described in this Privacy Policy.

10) Contact Us

If you choose to use our Services, any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or concerns about your privacy, please contact us at privacy@42entertainment.com.

(Last updated on 2/11/13)
